Bailey and Thurman families papers, circa 1882-1995
Emory University
Bailey and Thurman families papers, circa 1882-1995
Manuscript Collection No. 807
9.25 linear ft. (13 boxes), 22 oversized papers (OP), 4 bound volumes (BV)
Family papers of African American Baptist minister and church leader, Isaac G. and Susie E. Bailey and their daughter and son-in-law Sue Bailey and Howard Thurman and other members of the Bailey family. The collection tracks the political and religious pursuits of the family through three generations.
Emory University University Archives
Source
Gift, 1998.
Restrictions on access
Unrestricted access.
Biographical Note
Reverend Isaac George Bailey (1847-1914) was born in Arkansas City to Perry and Virginia Bailey. Educated at Branch Normal College in Pine Bluff, Bailey served as pastor of First Baptist Church in Dermott, Arkansas, and Log Bayou Church in Tillar Station, Arkansas. He also served as president of the Southeast District Industrial Baptist Academy in Dermott and as moderator of the South-East District Baptist Association. Isaac Bailey was a major force within the Arkansas Baptist Convention and worked closely with the National Negro Business League and the Arkansas Baptist College. In 1866, he married Winnie White. They had two children: Charles H. Bailey and Maude Bailey Frazier, who served as assistant principal of the South-East Industrial Academy.
In 1884, Bailey married Susie E. Ford. Susie E. Ford (d. 1948) was the daughter of Elvie, a slave, and T. S. Ford, a Mississippi plantation-owner. Isaac G. and Susie E. Bailey were prominent religious leaders who served as colporteurs for the American Baptist Publication Society, selling Bibles and other religious books throughout Arkansas. Susie Bailey attended Sumner High School and Normal School in St. Louis. She served as president of Southeast District Baptist Women's Association and as an agent for the Women's American Mission Baptist Home Mission Society. Susie and Isaac Bailey had nine children, six of whom died before adulthood.
The Baileys' youngest child Sue Elvie was born on August 3, 1903. She attended a school, in Washington, D. C., operated by Nannie Helen Burroughs, an associate of her mother, and later the Lucretia Mott School in Washington. She subsequently attended Spelman Seminary and then Oberlin College, where she obtained a bachelor's degree in music in 1926. After graduation from Oberlin, Ms. Bailey joined the Music Department at Hampton Institute. In the summer of 1928, she joined the staff of the Young Women's Christian Association as the National Secretary for Colleges in the South.
On June 12, 1932, Sue Bailey married Morehouse College graduate Howard Thurman. In the fall of 1932, the couple moved to Washington, D.C., where Howard Thurman took a position as professor of Theology at Howard University. In October of 1935, the Thurmans began a seven-month tour of India, Burma, and Ceylon. On this tour, they had a three-hour conversation with Mahatma Gandhi. In 1940, Mrs. Thurman served as the founding editor of the Aframerican Woman's Journal, the official organ of the National Council of Negro Women. She continued in that capacity until 1943. In 1944, the Thurmans and Presbyterian minister Alfred G. Fisk established the Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples in San Francisco. In 1949, Mrs. Thurman published Pioneers of Negro Origin in California. The Thurmans moved to Boston in 1953, where Dr. Thurman served as Dean of Marsh Chapel, Boston University, until 1966.
The Thurmans retired to San Francisco where they again became active in the Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples. Howard Thurman died in 1981. Mrs. Thurman died in San Francisco on December 25, 1996.
Scope and Content Note
The Bailey and Thurman families papers spans the years from 1882 to 1995. The collection tracks the political and religious pursuits of the family through three generations. It includes correspondence, writings, printed material, newspaper clippings, books from the Bailey library, photographs, legal documents, financial records, and general ephemera.
A large portion of the collection is made up of correspondence written to family members. The correspondence written to and by Isaac and Susie Bailey is of particular interest. It covers familial matters as well as those pertaining to the branches of the Baptist Missionary Association. In addition to their own letters, there is the correspondence to and from their children: Maude, vice principal of Southeast Industrial Academy; Isaac, Jr., a graduate of Howard University, printer/editor, and early member of Omega Psi Phi Fraternity; Dorcas Bailey; and Sue Bailey Thurman. The correspondence also includes a series of letters to Elias A. Morris, the son of Elias Camp Morris, prominent leader of the Arkansas Baptist Association and the National Baptist Convention. Additional material relates to Arkansas Baptist College, the Southeast Baptist Academy, the Southeast District Missionary Baptist Association, the Baptist Women's Southeastern District Association, and the Woman's American Baptist Home Mission Society.
Within this collection there are also a number of writings by the Bailey family. One section focuses on those speeches, lectures, and reports written by Isaac and Susie Bailey. Religious in nature, these writings, generally affiliated with the Arkansas Baptist Association or the Southeast Baptist Association, cover a broad range of topics from motherhood to Christian responsibility. Another small section in the collection contains minutes and reports, largely handwritten, relating to various Baptist conventions and organizations.
The collection also contains a fair amount of printed material dating from 1880 to 1995. A significant part of the printed material in the collection highlights the Baileys' leadership in the development of Baptist organizations in Southeast Arkansas. Many of these documents were printed by African-American publishers and presses. The more contemporary documents relate to the dealings of Sue (nee Bailey) and Howard Thurman. This information includes an article on the Thurmans' trip to India where they met with Mahatma Gandhi. There is also information related to their affiliations with Spelman and Morehouse Colleges. In addition to these early pieces, there are also articles on Susie Bailey, Howard Thurman, and Sue Bailey Thurman, as well as published copies of smaller books, including Sue Bailey Thurman's Pioneers of Negro Origin in California (1949).
The next two sections consist of newspapers and newspaper clippings. The newspapers range in date from 1893 to 1948, and they cover a broad range of political and religious topics. There are a number of copies of the Baptist Vangard, an African-American religious newspaper, as well as numerous copies of the St Louis Weekly Globe Democrat. The newspaper clippings cover a broad range of subjects, including, but certainly not limited to, obituaries of Bailey family members, tributes, and honors and awards for the Bailey-Thurman family members.
The largest, single component of the collection is the photographic section. Although the majority of the photographs are undated, they can be loosely dated from the 1880s to 1996 and have been divided into several categories. The first consists of the early photographs of the Bailey family members. The second contains the photographs of Howard Thurman and Sue Bailey Thurman. There are photographs of them alone and/or attending various functions, whether together or individually. There is also an array of photographs of Howard Thurman, from professional portraits to more casual images. There are many family photographs, professional photographs divided by organizational affiliation, and travel photographs, including photographs with Mahatma Gandhi. Finally, there are the photographs taken without either Sue Bailey or Howard Thurman. These photos vary in subject matter; they include images used to illustrate Sue Bailey Thurman's Pioneers of Negro Origin in California as well as images of well-known African Americans. Additionally, there are a large number of photographs of others, mostly unidentified, although there are prominent individuals featured, including Nathan I. Huggins (who was raised by the Thurmans) and Wole Soyinka. Finally, there are the negatives/slides and miscellaneous photographs.
There is a small amount of financial and legal records in the collection. This covers the period from the late 1800s to approximately 1947. The financial records include receipts covering a broad range of services from product orders to deed payments. There is also a folder of banking materials including bank statements, deposit slips, and bankbooks for Mrs. Susie Bailey. The legal section consists of insurance policies, real estate records, as well as miscellaneous legal items.
Finally, there are several items of ephemera. These include devotional books about mothers, a miniature hymnal, election memorabilia, and cloth maps.
Arrangement Note
Organized into nine series: (1) Correspondence, (2) Writing by the Bailey family, (3) Minutes and reports, (4) Printed material, (5) Photographs, (6) Legal and financial records, (7) Ephemera, (8) Collected material, and (9) Audiovisual material.
Selected Search Terms
Personal Names
Bailey, I. G. (Issac George), 1847-1914.; Bailey, Susie E., d. 1948.; Morris, Elias A.; Thurman, Howard, 1900-1981.; Thurman, Sue Bailey.
Corporate Names
Arkansas Baptist Association.; Arkansas Baptist College.; Arkansas Baptist State Convention.; Baptist Women's Southeastern District Association.; Morehouse College (Atlanta, Ga.); Southeast District Missionary Baptist Association.; Spelman College.; Woman's American Baptist Home Mission Society.
Topical Terms
African American clergy--Arkansas.; African American women--Arkansas.; African American Baptists--Arkansas.; African Americans--Arkansas--Religion; African American Baptists--Arkansas--Clergy.; Baptists--Missions--Arkansas.; Spouses of clergy--Arkansas.; Women in church work--Arkansas--Baptists.
Geographic Names
Pine Bluff (Ark.)--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre Terms
Photographs.
Occupation
Clergy.
Related Materials in Other Repositories
Howard Thurman study library, Morehouse College; Howard Thurman papers and Sue Bailey Thurman papers, Mugar Memorial Library, Boston University.
Related Materials in This Repository
Issac and Sue Bailey library and Howard and Sue Bailey Thurman personal library.
Description of Series
- Correspondence, 1855-1995, Series 1; Boxes 1 - 3
  - I. G. Bailey, 1882-1901 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - I. G. Bailey, 1903-1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - I. G. Bailey, 1910-1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - I. G. Bailey, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1883-1899 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1900-1904 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1905-1909 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1910-1914 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1915-1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1920-1925 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1926-1929 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1930-1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1940-1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Susie E. Bailey, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Susie E. Bailey, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, 1912-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, 1941-February 1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, 1948-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., 1906-1911 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., 1912-1913 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., 1914-1918 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dorcas Bailey, 1911-1917 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Maude Bailey, 1900-1909 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - E. A. Morris, 1906-1913 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1855-1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Writings by Bailey family, Series 2; Box 4 (folders 1 - 16)
  - Manuscript: "These Angels..," author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript: re Black History (incomplete), author unknown, holograph n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript: "The doctrine of the gospel is as salt..." author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript: "We must study foreign missions..." (incomplete), author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript: "The Munificence of Arkansas" author unknown, typescript, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript: "The Past Week," (incomplete), author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript of a sermon, author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript: Re: Southeast Baptist Academy, (incomplete) author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript: "Training of Children," Susie Bailey, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Speech: Address by Rev. I.G. Bailey at the 10th Anniversary of the Southeast District Association, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Speech: Susie Bailey regarding raising money for her school, holograph. n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Speech: Address at Meeting in District of Columbia (incomplete), author unknown, typescript, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Speech: Welcome Address to Sisters of the Central District, author unknown, holograph (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Speech: Address to the Sisters of the Bible Band regarding temperance, author unknown, holograph, n.d (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Speech: "Her Life as Mother" / Tribute/eulogy to Sister Davis," author unknown, holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Speech: Welcome Address to a woman’s organization, author unknown, typescript, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Minutes and reports, 1893-1946, Series 3; Box 4 (folders 17-29)
  - Baptist Women’s Southeast Arkansas Association, president’s report, E.A. Smith (author), typescript, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Executive Board (organization unknown), minutes, holograph, July 16, 1893 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Executive Board of Mother’s Conference, report, holograph, December 29 1894 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board of the Southeast District Industrial Academy, minutes, holograph, March 20, 1905 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board of the Mothers Fireside Schools of Pine Bluff, report, Susie Bailey (author), n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Home Missionary Society, report, Susie Bailey (author), holograph, November 1930 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Howard University freshman and sophomore class minute book, I.G. Bailey, 1911-1913 (Box BV1)
  - Moderator’s report, (organization unknown), I.G. Bailey (author), Typescript, November 3, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Southeast District Association, report, Mrs. R.N. Davis (author), Holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Southeast District Women’s Association, report, Susie Bailey (author), Holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Southeast District Women’s Association, report, Susie Bailey (author), Holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Superintendent of Sunday Schools of Bethany Church in Dermott, report, Susie Bailey (author), January 1946 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Listing of Stockholders Officers (organization unknown), holograph, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Printed material, 1885-1986, Series 4; Box 4 (folders 30-59) - Box 5 and OP1-2
  - Pamphlets, brochures, broadsides
  - Arkansas Baptist College, Dedication of Library, May 23, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Arkansas Baptist College, "Front Elevation of New Building" (broadside) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, Conventional Letter, Little Rock August 23-28, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, Conventional Letter, Little Rock, November 21-25, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, Fiftieth Anniversary Golden Jubilee, November 19-25, 1917, Little Rock: Vanguard Print (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, Minutes of the Nineteenth Annual Session, August 23-28, 1918, Little Rock: Press Printing Company (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Arkansas Baptist Women’s Association, Minutes of the Forty-Fourth Annual Session, June 1918, Little Rock: The Baptist Vanguard (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Bailey, I. G., Circular Letter of the Southeast District for ca. June 1894 (4 copies) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Bailey, I. G., Rules and Regulations of the Literal Society, Arkansas City: Arkansas: Journal Print, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Bailey, Susie, Bible Class Report. Women’s American Mission Baptist Home Mission Society, n.d. (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Bailey, Susie, Broadside, n.d. (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Baptist Women’s Southeastern District Association (held with The Friendship Baptist Church, Baxter, Arkansas), Programme, July 30-August 1, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Baptist Women’s Southeastern District Association (held with The Saint Morion Baptist Church), August 26-28, 1905, Programme (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Baptist Women’s Southeastern Association, Proceedings of the Thirteenth Annual Session, August 26-28, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Baptist Women’s Southeast Arkansas Association, Minutes of the 17th Annual Session, August 23-26, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Blackall, C. R., "Beautiful Praise": An Order of Service for Children’s Day 1890, American Baptist Publication Society (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Blue, L. W., History of the Southeast District Baptist Association, n.d. (incomplete) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Booker, Joseph A., How Shall We Raise It?, Little Rock: Vanguard Print, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Booker, Joseph A., The Self-Education of the Negro, Little Rock: Arkansas Baptist College (reprint of Baptist Home Mission Monthly August 1903) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Catholic Interracial Council of Washington, Contemporary Religious Paintings, Barnett Aden Gallery, Washington, D. C., October 17-November, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Chanticleer Farm Chamber Music Festival, Program, September 10, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - "China’s Millions" (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - The Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples, 32nd Anniversary Celebration, Newsletter, October 3, 10, 17, 24 and 31, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - The Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples, Order of Worship, August 31, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Delany, E.B. "Our Little Light Bearer," Foreign Mission Board National Baptist Convention, Louisville, Kentucky, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Dixie to Broadway: An exhibition of Black Americans on Stage, 1977 (4 copies) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Dolls for Democracy, "Toys Aid Thurman Campaign for Understanding," n.d. (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Douglass Quilt Exhibit, Howard Thurman Trust Programs (3 copies) and Posters (2 copies) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Dunbar High School, Washington, D.C., Annual Commencement, June 20, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - First Baptist Church, Goddard, Kansas, January 1, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Foard, Elder F.C.V. "I Am on the Right Side," Memphis, Tennessee, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Four County Track Meet, Dermott, Arkansas, Program, April 13, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Gospel of St. Luke (Susie Bailey’s copy) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Harris, H. H. (ed), The Advanced Quarterly: International Lessons, Philadelphia: American Baptist Publication Society, October 1892 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hawkins, Thomas [Dean] and Wallace Capel [M.D.], A Meritorious Tribute, June 14, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Howard College Dramatic Club (broadside), April 15, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Howard University Calendar, "Twelve Reproductions from the Living Madonna in Art Series," n.d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Howard University, Commencement Program and Invitation, June 1917 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Howard University Journal, Editorial Election, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Sister M, Funeral Program, November 3, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Wallace Van, "The Countee Cullen Memorial Collection at Atlanta University," The Crisis, May 1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Johnson, Georgia Douglas, Poem, "I Gaze Into the Sun, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Koshland, Daniel Sr., In Memory, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Moore, Joanna, "I Will Hear What God the Lord Will Speak," September 4, 1891 (Photograph in OP3) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Moran, Ulysses Simpson, Funeral Program, September 3, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Morehouse College, Interment Services for Sue Bailey Thurman, May 15, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Morris, E. C., Thirty-Sixth Annual Address, Baptist State Convention of Arkansas, November 20, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - National Baptist Convention, Music and Official Programme, Twenty-Ninth Annual Session, September 15-21, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - National Baptist Convention, U.S.A, Program, Praise Services and Mortgage-Burning Ceremonies of the Morris Memorial Building, Nashville, Tennessee, December 10, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Baptist Young People’s Union Board, BYPU Supplies, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Nurses’ Sunday Lecture Series (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Peabody, Lucy W., Everyland Children, Central Committee on the United Study of Foreign Missions, Lynn, Massachusetts: Nichols-Ellis Press, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - The Peruna Almanac for 1900 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pope, Howard W, "Anyone Can Be Saved and Kept By Jesus" (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Preacher’s Helper, Vol. XXVI, No. 3, March 1909 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Raising up a Prophet... (pp. 86-91), Text by Sudarshan Kapur (See Box 8 FF6 for photographs) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Ethel. "Have You Seen Woman: The Eternal Question," advertisement, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Trudi, Sue Bailey Thurman: Building Bridges to Common Ground, Boston: Trustees of Boston University, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Southeast District Baptist Academy, Closing Exercises, April 21-22, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Southeast Baptist Academy, Program, April 12, 1908 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Southeast Baptist Association, Proceedings of the Twenty-Third Annual Session, November 1906 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Southeast Baptist Women’s Association (1st Session), held with Mt. Calvary Baptist Church, Baxter, Arkansas, July 1897 (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Southeast District Baptist Association, Proceedings of the Twenty Ninth Annual Session, held with St. Paul Baptist Church, Dermott, Arkansas, October 29-November 1, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Southeast District Baptist Women’s Association, Program of the 32nd Annual Session. August 1929 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Southeast District Baptist Women’s Association, Program of the 33rd Annual Session, August, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Southeast District Baptist Women’s Association, Program of the 34th Annual Session, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Southeast District Missionary Baptist Association, Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Session, held with Friendship Baptist Church, Baxter, Arkansas, July 30-August 3, 1890, Little Rock: Vanguard Print, Baptist College (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Southeast District Sunday School Convention, Minutes of the Third Annual Session, May 11-13, 1893, Little Rock: Vanguard Print (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Southeastern District Association, Program of the Minister’s and Deacon’s Union, June 1912 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Southeastern District Baptist Association of Arkansas, Programme of the Twenty Fourth Annual Session, held with Silver Mount Baptist Church, Hudspeth, Arkansas, October 30-November 3, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Spelman Seminary, Piano Recital by Advanced Pupils, May 3, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Spelman Seminary, Piano Recital, April 22, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - State Agricultural and Mechanical Institute, Normal, Alabama, Religious Service, January 28, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - State Federation of Colored Women’s Clubs, Proceedings of the Annual Sessions, 1913-1914, Fort Smith, Arkansas: J. W. Rice Printing, Co. (Box 5, Folder 42)